http://www.johnstoncc.edu/privacy-notice/

This website uses cookies as well as similar tools and technologies to understand visitors' experiences. By continuing to use this website, you consent to Johnston Community College’s usage of cookies and similar technologies. Learn more.
I Accept
Skip to Main Content
Appointment-Plus
Blackboard
Hours
Library
Search for Classes
Student
Johnston Community College (“JCC”) is committed to delivering information services
that recognize and respect users’ privacy concerns. This Privacy Notice is intended
to inform you of our general policies and practices regarding our collection, use,
and disclosure of the information that you submit to us and that we collect from you
during your use of the www.johnstoncc.edu website.
The types of information we collect may vary depending on the specific JCC site you
visit or application you use. Accordingly, this Privacy Notice is intended to be a
general statement and may be supplemented by more specific privacy notices that pertain
to personal information exclusively associated with a specific department, unit or
function.
Our Information Collection and Use Practices
Information you submit voluntarily through our websites, such as your name, email,
or other contact information, may be collected by JCC to respond to your inquiries,
as well as for internal marketing and development purposes.
JCC websites may use online data entry forms to collect personally identifiable information,
including your name and contact information (email, address, telephone number) and
other identifiers in order to allow you to provide website feedback, register for
events, or use JCC’s online applications and services.
We may reveal personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third
parties:
if you request or authorize it;
if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you;
if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental
and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of
Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights,
property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for
fraud protection etc.);
if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers
to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance,
providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or
as otherwise described in this Privacy Notice or in a more specific privacy notice
associated with a particular department, unit or function.
We may share information that does not personally identify you without restriction.
Cookies and Website Analytics
We use cookies and similar technology to collect aggregate (non-personal) information
about website usage by all of our visitors and to help us remember you and your preferences
when you revisit the websites. These cookies may stay on your browser into the future
until they expire or you delete them. We also use technology to remember you the next
time you log in. Some of these cookies are erased when you close your browser window
and some persist for a period of time. Further general information about cookies and
how they work is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. You can decline cookies by adjusting your browser settings but some features of
the websites may not function.
We may allow selected third parties to place cookies through the website to provide
us with better insights into the use of the website or user demographics or to provide
relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a user’s
online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our
website.
Many JohnstonCC.edu websites use Google Analytics (or other similar web analytics
tools) to collect information about visitor traffic and behavior. This allows us to
identify usage trends and to improve the performance and content of our websites.
We do not use this tool to collect or store your personal information, and it cannot
be used to identify who you are.
You can use the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on to disable tracking by Google Analytics.
We currently do not use technology that responds to do-not-track signals from your
browser.
Access and Choice
You can choose not to receive certain emails from us by “unsubscribing” using the
instructions in any email you receive from us. This will not stop us from sending
emails about your account or education with us.
Updates to Privacy Notice
JCC reserves the right to modify this privacy notice at any time. We encourage visitors
to frequently check this page for any changes to this Privacy Notice. If we make changes,
we will post an updated effective date below. Your continued use of this site after
any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
